Come to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
With a rhythm
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Whoa
Hearts and the balance, every card and open door
Feel the romance in every arcane world
I'm sitting here, I'm just sitting here looking at you in a state of shock.
Let's see. Uh, it's gone.
What? In a state of shock, I was watching you.
Why did you just hear discord? You were just on my discord?
Oh no, I made a discord. I didn't even remember.
Remember when you sent me that picture of a gerbil?
call you remember that call right I never I asked you for nude for your new
photos and he's having a picture of South Park let me weeks the gerbil from
South Park yeah that wasn't it I wasn't a new right
It wasn't a good it wasn't I know that was a good episode
But it didn't make any sense for what I asked and then you sent me a picture of a giant cartoon gerbil
He asked for nerds and so I just see you there in sir side of my asshole. Oh my god
I'm so happy I was hoping that wasn't the joke
Oh
Hi guys. I was looking for like keep saying that there's some option for vertical streaming
like and it's like oh it's so cool you can do this and this and this but I don't see
it in here. We see vertical streaming. I mean does anybody know how to do it? Oh. Anybody
I don't see anything like that.
I don't know.
Is this cinematic, Leah?
Maybe there needs to be guests on or something.
I don't know.
Until then, I'm gonna do full screen.
Hi guys, how are you?
Hi, you like that, Nick?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Hey, shepherd.
I rogue nomad, how are you?
Oh, look.
How'd you get a mod how'd that happen I don't know make a DS card
Hi, babe, yeah, look who's here tonight. Oh Lola's here. It's Lola. Were you
Lola you get Lola was under the covers. Oh, you're making your face making your little sour sour to his face
It's okay. You're she went under the covers what happened
You know tricks are to walk on top of you. He's our growling. He was walking on top of us, right?
And then he he got another the covers and you you ran out
Okay, that's your son, right?
Well, okay, I can finally hear again, you know, oh, yeah, I'm getting some coffees tonight. I don't know if I'll like
I don't know if I'll open up this tonight. This is the idea. I do have this too
I got also a new deck today. This is the Kabbalah
Kabbalistic tarot I
Seen like a similar deck to it on the show and I've never been able to find it
It's really cool. It has like a Hebrew letters and it has like
Um, the, what's it called?
The correspondence of the Hebrew letter with certain cards.
So let's have a look at the deck.
We'll do an unboxing of this deck.
Oh, come on, Katie.
Is that, is that Rudy phone?
Wait a second.
Hold on.
So let's have a look at this deck and look at the fool, for example.
Okay, hold on, Rudy.
Let's check it out.
Hi, Rudy.
Hey, Rudy.
Hey!
I'm fighting with Rudy.
Let me just jump over and roll this over.
OK, so this is the certificate of authenticity.
Ooh, I wonder if hopefully this is a real deck,
by the certificate of authenticity.
It looks legit, OK?
If you look at certain Kabbalistic texts,
they do have this kind of the arch, the pillars.
But for example, here's Lemmat.
This is the fool card.
Okay, so you see the fool and is the the element of air. This is the fool and it shows you it's up from Kether to
What is it, Tippereth? I can't, I mean it's a little small
It's a little bit small. It's hard to see a little bit, but I think it's
I need to get another light on but then it's a and then it's got the French name and that this is the letter ALEF
ALEF, that's like a letter A in Hebrew
So I mean I study and look at what is that little dog? Yeah
And he has a walking stick and he's a walking stick and a
And a little back a summer. How are you? Okay? Okay? We want to come so this is a cool deck. By the way, I have steady
Kabbalah, I learned the Hebrew alphabet. I'm not like, you know
The proficient in Hebrew or anything. I do know the letters most of the letters, but you know pretty well by heart
they're considered magical in
Kabbalah and
You know, there's three these three that are combinations known as the names of God and
They have the certain different powers to them
Including like, you know, very
Magical things like time travel
In certain ways, okay, so
You look into sitting come all I mean it's also like kind of a new age cabala and then there's like you know
I guess the original cabala was
There is in Spain in Spain these books started coming out and they were supposedly like rediscovered books, but they're probably you know
Written more recently because they didn't come out with a printing press until like the 1500s, right?
And so it's kind of fanciful
I know they did have scrolls and things like that but these scrolls were not these big books like these are some big books
But
You can just use your imagination a little bit like you do is like you have to do with some spirituality because then it does the
If you don't work to the system, it doesn't work. Hey there. Let's see
Doc
Oh, deep woo! Is that woo? Hey, what's up?
What's up, woo?
Or, um, oceans? Hey, what's up, oceans?
The ocean's deep woo. Okay, sorry, I need my glasses tonight.
I saw some of, I think, do you know where you do it using some, or oceans?
We're using, um, trying out some AI, because I saw some cool, um, some cool, um, pictures of, uh, of you on your, uh, YouTube page.
So it looks like you might be having some fun with that
And it's good
Chat GPT actually, I don't know if it's available for everybody right now
Or it's just like I'm a plus GPT user. So it's like I pay the 20 bucks
To get like, you know, they have a deep agent and I I'm on the 5.0
But they just this was from 4.0 to 5.0. I have a couple like these affogato
Have you heard of avocado not avocado affogato?
I think it's my copies here. I ordered a couple copies
So I was like, I've been sleeping all day like I just keep getting sleepy
I've taken like probably like five or six naps, which is like way too many naps. I'm gonna take my coffee safe one
But I was like I don't want to like get tired if I like do a show so
I'm gonna get a bunch of coffee and see what happens. Let me see if it here
That's not even here yet
Okay, if you get messages like oh, it's dark outside, you know
I like for the guy, but okay. I'm back. Hi kitty cats. I'm gonna open some cans of food for the cats
Okay
This is what they like
The first these with these things. Okay. All right, kitty cats
Can you get here?
Okay, I can get okay
So how is your day? It's Saturday, huh?
Hi, we're here
Okay, did I post the link yet?
Hi guys use Pixar. Oh, that's cool
Oh, use Pixar.
OK, that's good.
We'll still try to, you can do the same similar thing
where you can say, put your picture,
you just attach your picture to the chat GPT.
You know, it's free and everything.
And then you can say, do this to this picture.
Do this, do the hair like this.
Do, make me look like 1979.
All kinds, you can say whatever you want.
Oh, you're practicing now?
OK.
You're doing some RB practice right now. Hey Vicky. How are you?
Vicky yeah, Vicky wrote me yesterday. She's on a on Tiktok
her her her screen name is a little bit a
Little bit of an adult. I would say an adult you make that not to call you up
But I won't tell you what I won't tell you what it is that the name was but yeah, she was
She was on a new account because
She got banned for several years. I don't know what happened. Okay
We're passing through art through cuz RV practice. What is RV practice? So are you practicing?
The thing on the RV. What does that mean? What are you doing up there? Oh, oh the cat here something or something
Hey, Lola, what are you doing? Look at her?
Lola
What are you doing?
Oh, she's going nuts. She's going up Lola. She's just running over the room. Oh my gosh. She pulled off your eight inch cucumber online
My god
You pulled it off
Like detachment I
Wish I was eight inches long. I'm
unfortunately
I'm like I am like a lot like Howard Stern that
I think I have like maybe like a two inch, two inch, sure.
It's really embarrassing, but you know,
maybe it's a growing on a show or oh, to completion.
Okay.
Well, good luck with that.
Good luck with that.
You know, hope it's okay.
Don't lose it.
How would they get a safe place to put it?
Right, put it in a safe place.
Preferably a girlfriend's vagina.
Or your boyfriends, but whatever you in the room makes sense you I don't really know
Okay, so yeah, I have a new product to recommend this is the
It's called the
Year something how long does it call it's called the my box?
Is it like a whole man, it was called
Ear cleaner with camera. Okay. It's called sole ear. Okay. This was like 12 bucks on Amazon. I didn't get like the
Yeah, team who won which is like six bucks
But it's a full camera and I don't know if I'm gonna demonstrate it for you because it is so weird like it goes
You know you put it in your ear has a camera on it, right?
And then you can go and you can find out where like the deposit is or whatever and start digging for like hours
I wish it was easier. I mean, it's like it is easy, but it's like I wish I was like, you know
Take me like a little while to get it good
It's like you don't want to go too far and it's like you want to get it exactly
It's kind of like it. Yes, like learn how to move the opposite way than on the camera and stuff like that. He rude
but
Little you need this to say I can hear now. I could I was like kind of like
I had not cleaned my ears for a while,
and so I got some Q-tips like recently,
and then when I used the Q-tips,
it just clogged my ears completely,
and I've been like deaf and off balance,
and I was like, hey, Root, hey Root.
So I know it's kind of gross, but if you guys I mean, so it's just like, you know, this happens like it's true
This is inside of your ear. I did not know the inside of my ear was that hairy and I oh my god
And it was clogged. I mean, I'm sorry if it's disgusting. I'm sorry if it was disgusting
This is what's good about YouTube is that gets little cigarettes on you too tight. Oh, yeah
So, I don't know if I'm banned from that liquor store yet.
Um, it could very well be.
Um, but it's okay.
Um, I have to, we'll just start walking to 7-eleven or something like that.
I think my neighbor will come help me fix the bike.
You know, I had a little bit of an issue with the bike again.
After he fixed the batteries for me, I fucked up the bike again.
I don't even know if I
Very frustrated I just feel like stupid I just feel stupid because it was finally I was waiting all this time
I was like, please come over please fix it and then it's like finally like he was able to and then I fucked it up again
but
Here's a bike it should be not impossible to fix right it's like just like kind of like maybe something popped out and
He's gonna screw it needs to just have the chain put it back on in the lock cut off
I can't even figure out if it like the lock is like stuck jammed within the key. It's just like it's a mess. It's a mess. I
Don't know how I got it home. Okay. You know, I just had like walk it home with like the okay
No one's coming up hold on you bite my phone
Yeah, I'm in a kind of better mood. I think it was good to get so much sleep and I was having good dreams
I've been dreaming about like I mean I have stuff on a
Okay
Wow, okay
Hmm
Hold on, okay, so I don't like it. I wouldn't usually share messages. I
Just like to
Look at the trouble for sure
Okay, well person says forget that exists, so I won't I won't use their name, okay
This will just be anonymous messages
Should I read it?
I don't know if I should read it.
You don't know who it's from.
It's all the obvious, but.
Anyway, honestly, it just told me, forget that I, again,
forget I don't exist.
Oh, shit, the typing.
OK, never mind, never mind, never mind.
I'm not going to say anything.
It's like, I feel like.
Feel like yes horrible things were like the horrible things were said that I never ever like laughed anything that was said about this person
I never laughed. I never agreed. I never you know, and it's like yeah, I
Should have been faster about me kicking the person off and blah blah blah blah
Yeah, I never agreed with anything and it's like I feel like this person
The whole issue is
It's like this person I really like like a lot and I
Feel like this person likes me at one point and it's like just like they haven't
I don't know
I won't say they hate me, but it feels like they do but
Hi Christine, how are you Christine change your name?
You know bother me. Yeah, but then they're watching right now. They're testing and I'll just get more shit
It's like I said the part where those things
I just that was just cut and then the other saying I was and by the way
They should just address it with them
But they're saying I was prank calling them or something pretending to be somebody I was not I was not that character
That was actually somebody else and I can even show you like I want to show you all show you my phone
I won't show the number. I won't show the message or anything
I'm gonna show you that it wasn't me because this person was texting me to
And they said I
Have to hide the number look look
You see it
So it's not me. It wasn't me. It was somebody else and they touched me too. What day was this?
This was July 7th
So whatever you're saying that I was pretending to making fun of you by being that person I was not
so
That's it
Meena is like some character that's very calling me one day and was like
Saiki it's Mika and it was like and then
It's not for the other person was laughing that day about it. I don't know man. I'm not they're mad about that. Okay, whatever, okay, I'm
It is like
Like I said, it hurts when like there's like people that are like not enemies, but like people that don't like me
You know that do that stuff, but it's like when somebody
I'll consider my like best friend does it it's like, okay
Anyway, forget about I just saw the message and they're kind of threw me off a little bit
But uh, I'll forget about it. So I don't want to
call that person
But
Yeah, okay, we can move so we're both upset. It's like we can't is there's no resolution. There's no resolution to it
It's like it's gonna be like okay. Well
So it does back to like the first issue like months ago where somebody said something I did kick them off the show
It was an inappropriate thing to say. It's been gone over a million times. I don't agree with it
I don't like I don't want it said I don't I don't you know, I think it's offensive and
ridiculous but
And I right I can't control and I know they can't control what people comes out of people's mouth
Is that I didn't tell him to kick off anybody. I would like
Be defended
Yeah, then the Lulu, you know, I've been to Luiz that is not Christine. Yes, Christine
It's not it is Christine. It's Christine. She changed your he changed your name, right?
I think, I mean, yes, but she's still a mod,
so it must be the same Christine.
And Vindaloo, so Vindaloo, I think of like Vindaloo,
there's an episode of South Park called
something in Vindaloo, let me see if my coffee's here.
Well, something in Vindaloo, and it's about like Cartman.
It's Cartman, like in Butters, like he,
he like pretends he has a virtual reality.
Thing and he puts it on butters, but it's like actually like see it's like snorkel goggles or something
And so it's like actually real and butters thinks he's on VR and then he like goes out and gets arrested by like stabbing some
Or he gets that and so then
Cartman gets stuck in like the virtual reality
You to change everyone's name to the YouTube channel, how does mine look now you see well I see hold on they did
That would change my name to something hold on let me see if they change it
Yeah, they did they change it to the YouTube channel well, that's okay
So now I'm okay
Well, maybe that's better for this channel because it's like now I can just like have the tarot under the
Let's take talk and put it in the description sometimes I guess too
Okay, anyway, the person that's mad. I mean, don't be mad. I'm just expressing myself and I'm not like in the best mood about things
It's just in general I'm in a bad mood lately and that's like I wake up
Maybe like throw it kind of a good mood and then I put on the show or the first thing I hear is like
My name being brought up again and then in a very negative way and then like everybody there just pretty pretty much like oh
Yeah, yeah, he's the terrible person
Or whatever they're saying
I'm gonna I'll let it go so I don't want to cause any more
It's a little mad enough of me
Enough I'm enough hatred coming at me right now. I don't need to like
store the
pot
Let me see I'm just gonna check out what my food is. Oh my
Hi rude. So here's Rudy. Hey rude. Rudy's like a little your kitchen cat really likes to be on the kitchen counter
Why?
You like to lay in the kitchen counter. You like to knock over dishes and stuff. Why?
He's very cute
Try fixing the problem and being a better person. Okay, so Christine. Can you take that person out?
Please just like hide them
Hey, Jamie, how are you?
I have many to learn, I don't know
What's very scary he's not listened to any criticism very scared. What is the criticism?
What would you just say first of all you said I didn't hear it was said and I did I went and it was Arthur on the phone
saying oh, why didn't you be at psyche's channel? It's because he's some kind of rifter and
Everyone's laughed and agreed
And then they're like, oh, yeah, we can charge people to come on panel again, which is not true
So I say and then also it's why all I said was like well
I had 45 people in my chat last night. So I'm not doing too bad. I mean good month. So he's wrong
And then she then she's like, oh, well, I don't she's like well
Yeah, he's gonna be bad at me because someone said this and that I'm like, no, I know it's not your fault what they're saying
But we're gonna be nice
Say hey, you know, I don't know
But anyway
Okay, yeah. Christine, can you take down the, or Jamie, or Rogue Nomad mod? Can you just, um, can you, um, hide that person, please?
Please.
I can do it. I mean, it just will take me a minute. Hold on.
It's like, I'm not in the mood.
I'm well aware of my faults, right?
It's like, yes, be a better person.
What does that mean, be a better person?
I'm pretty much the best person I can be.
Then you say, yeah, there's this person saying,
okay, just to be annoying.
I just say, can people start annoying me like this?
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Can people start annoying me like this?
Oh, hold on.
What was that?
Oh, my thank you.
Thank you.
I don't know who that was, but it's like it just wasn't some random person. It feels like it's like
somebody I probably blocked before trying to like just leave it in, right? Yeah, I just recognize it.
Do we have to yell at you? Why do you want to yell at me? Thank you. Thank you so much.
Dismal papers, what's that so this is called the affogato it's like a vanilla latte with like an egg or the vanilla
This is like a vanilla milkshake with like strong coffee in the bottom of it. It's really good
It's like really good, huh? What are the best one of the best things I've ever had oh
Dismissal I was like some dismal news. Okay, so his things being dismissed. Okay, congratulations Santa Santa Nick
guys
Nick was arrested just at Santa Claus last year,
are you before?
It has been dismissed.
Congratulations, Nick.
Okay, so I have the link up here.
Here's the link.
We'll do open panel Saturday night.
We'll do, I'm not even gonna bring up sponsoring the panel.
It would be, it's always nice
when people do sponsor the panel.
I do appreciate it,
but I'm like, I'm just done with being accused
of like charging everybody and, you know, it's like, oh boy.
I want to bring it up.
Let's have a, have a Thon meet, Thon meet tonight.
Okay.
I'll sponsor my own panel.
But it is Saturday night.
I didn't see anybody else really live.
So I was like, okay.
Well, if everyone wants to hang out, I'll host it.
So I hope you guys have fun.
I'm going to pin my link.
Yeah, so anyway, so my sister's in Croatia tonight,
or this weekend, so it's a little hard getting
hold of her recently, but that's kind of weird.
Croatia keeps being brought up, huh?
Okay
Open my link
Hi, Johnny
Yeah, I got as far as like okay, well, and so I mean I was like
I'm tired, and I'm not in the best mood, and I'm like,
okay, well, let's all just order a bunch of coffee.
So it can be a waste.
So things can get extensive around here,
but I'm not gonna say anything.
You can be so rude to people and drop your closest friend
when you find someone new friend on YouTube to get a row.
Guys, who is this person?
Who is this person?
I need I like I need to like talk to my mods better about like what I don't want
There's people that are like saying that stuff
it's like they're obviously like somebody else that I've kicked out or something like that and
jumping on the I
Don't want to hear like I don't want I'd like to hear the people like okay, so chat GPT is like
I want to hear the truth, especially from something like ChatGPT, which is supposed to be some kind of unbiased thing, but they programmed ChatGPT to be super nice.
And so people are going crazy right now because it's just reinforcing whatever the person thinks is a good idea.
And the chat PTPG telling us oh, that's a good idea do this do this and some of them are not good things to do
Like this some people think that they're saving the world or something like that
Like oh, I want to save the world and you know take out these criminals and I want to you know
Unalive these people and it's like okay. That's a good idea that you should do that
But you know it's like it's so and so people are literally going insane
So that's what I want from people is like be honest with me
But I can tell the difference between just being honest with me and then trying to pile on or trying to a very sad
Okay, so you mods. Can we do the test now? Okay, do you see you see?
I don't know who that is. It's the same person the third time in a row
Because it or else they would be it would be more than one at a time, right?
Okay, I
Mean it's the exact same person. It's even the same. Hold on. It's the same. Oh, thank you. Thank you. Now, you know
But and I know I've been very like, oh, don't you know don't worry about it, but it's like it's like getting to be
little much
I'm just trying to have I'm just trying to chill man. I'm trying to chill, right?
I'm trying to chill like mr. Big Pikes or whatever, right?
So I might like express a little myself a little bit and I like to
You know, I've always been like that on my show where it's like I tell you how I feel and if I'm not find a bad mood
I'll be in a bad move, but it's like I'm trying to be in a good mood and stuff. I don't want to be fake
I don't want to be but
You know, I'm just like a little bit of set right now
Trying to you know better move and it's like and it's just like I'm being bothered by by certain things
Okay, so they're gonna keep coming
Here come see look
Look look look look look
Look you see I mean it's like one after the other I mean it's like
That's what that's how it goes sometimes
Probably sick or something because I did kick sick off. Yeah
Hey Vicki, thank you
I'm fine. I'm actually fine. It's like I'm getting irritated now because now it's like for the fifth time the person who's been back just saying like annoying stuff
Reminds me of sick
So I'll just see I just but it's good because they'll just keep revealing themselves and I'll just keep deleting them
You think it's mr. Big Pipes. Yeah
Mm-hmm
But guys you see you see now. It's like the six six account
And it's not anything helpful is it's like just name-calling it's like basically
Accusations and it's just like the same kind of it's obviously the same person
So anyway, we'll get we'll get it all. We'll get it all sort of it doesn't bother you what they're saying
It's just bothered. Yeah, he's ranting about the trailer
Yeah, I remember that where he was like
Mr. Big Pipe's actually like he rented this trailer from some guy and then caused some damage to it and was like hey
Well, it's like I'll just buy the part you see like you can read you can repair it yourself
I'll just I'll just buy the part the guys like no, I'd rather go through insurance and you know
and have it repaired professionally.
And then he's like, well, the water inside the trailer
tasted like ass or something like that.
And with poisoning me, I'm gonna sue you for poison.
I mean, it's just like that kind of like annoying.
It's one of the nights guys, it'll be okay though.
But thank you, Miles, and I'm sorry,
I don't mean to get like.
Like bitchy or anything. I'm sorry. I don't mean it. It's not it's not you. It's like them
Yeah, no one called me a name. It's not a name. It's not name calling necessarily. It's more like a
general attitude
And I recognize energy I recognize the energy so even if it's said in different ways or whatever I recognize the attitude
Where it's like it's just basically
Putting me down, okay
No, I don't I'm out of weed. I
Don't have weed. I don't have
I'm practically already I don't know it'll just be it'll be enough. It'll be a tough week
You know, it'll be another tough week last week. It's pretty tough week
This week will be a tough week, but you know what? I'll get through it. I'll get through I've gotten through every week before
So it'll be okay, okay
You know, I'll be I'll be okay
Okay, I'm worried more I want more worried more about other people than I felt
Yeah, the people put my panel get down you just let it happen normally guys, okay, so
Guys do you feel I mean and I knew it's the same people it's the same guys now
He's back on the seventh 30th account put down the panel guests
Well, do I get put down constantly on panels? Hold on. I'll do it myself
Just keep going guys if you see it just just keep this you see if you see them back just keep going
No, I don't think he's okay. I don't like what he's saying
He's bringing up that same shit. Oh, I'm putting down people put down the panel guests
Well, some panel guests deserve to be put down. I mean, maybe you can say I deserve to put down sometimes with some panel guests
Yeah, they're a panel guest that will not only put down other people, but they'll put down
They'll put down, you know me they'll put down
The show and they'll basically just shit all over it and then it's like and so
But, you know, some things that don't deserve, you know, some people don't deserve it, some people do, I guess, I don't know.
But, you know, I can't control again. The thing is, do I say it? Do I sit there agreeing with it? Do I kick the person off the panel?
Which I have many times. I've deleted shows. I've deleted shows at the request of people because they didn't like what was said on the show.
And so I'm always very open to talking about things.
It is in the heat of the moment sometimes.
I was sometimes a little bit drunk before.
And then there are some people that
was their personality.
I deal with trolley communities.
I mean, if I basically took off everybody that
said something wrong, I would have no guess on the show.
Everyone would be banned, because most everybody
has said something that is like.
Right and he was yeah, and it's like but then there's such a difference between goofing on which is like the Howard Stern style
Like you know with me with the high
Kind of goofing on him in a fun playful way
Rather than
In like a cruel way, whatever. Okay, Christina Christina some other people you're in the new song
I'll play the new song. It's and maybe I need to redo it, but it's a it's a cute song. I'll redo it
I like how it came out here. Hold on, I'll play it for senior in the song
Well, Psyche's in his speedo, stars and stripes parade, fish tacos on the table, another wild charade, he's hitting on the straight men, come on, lose that shirt, meanwhile, Bita's on the hotline, yell until it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps, like dodgeball in the gym, Canada drive.
Christine's with Fawzi Bear
Arthur's stirring pots like he's cooking up a scare
Trucker at old rumbles in salmon's chasing views DJ
Electrous cartoon face
It's here in-
Why is Arthur still talking?
Org, I'm first Arthur.
Okay, that was cute.
Right, robot, that is a, that's quite a question.
And also, how does he think he's a sex symbol?
I mean, it's like, he's like 300 pounds with his,
you know, every button of his shirt on buttons.
it's kind of like, you know, a little bit nauseating.
But anyway, I won't talk negatively about people.
Even though he says, we hate, we don't like you,
we don't like you, I'm like, you know,
the devil or some kind of like, you know,
the worst person in the world.
I know, I know.
Guys, and these are people I've never done any,
like, really, like there's,
but nobody said anything about them on the show,
they just don't like me, and it's okay,
you're not supposed to like,
you don't have to like everybody,
I'm not into like hate washing. I mean, it's like even those people like that I have trolled like Miss Netta
Which I've just I've you know, I admit I've trolled Miss Netta, but I like Miss Netta like a lot
You know, and it's like my trolling Miss Netta is
It's just like it's just funny. I don't know there's a difference. I don't know if there's a difference
Yeah, I mean it's like well, let's see Billy Bass person
Yeah, basically
California, I think they get about $1,000 a month, like 500, 500, 600 cash, and then
like 300 food stamps. I don't know where he is. You're just waking up, asking
Siri who's staying at. You play this song the other morning, you woke up to, it was
I'll do one more the rules. I'll play the rules song
Was it rules or is it?
No hate speech don't test that line don't care if it's soft day to hard our time you say it you've gone
Don't play confused this ain't that show we don't make those moves no slander
Yeah, I said what I said you toss more fake dirt than a reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat false accusations man cut that crap
Dumb things why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place
Posting addresses like it's Halloween. You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity. We beg and plead
I'll Dean no one wants your balls on screen flirty diamonds stop the solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
that
I don't know. I don't know if it ended or something. It stopped in the middle. It's fine.
You're confused. Why are you confused?
Because the thing that is, you said, what did you say?
You said, ghost is up there for hours,
calling people, C-U-N-T-S and idiots,
but you are disengaged.
Oh, okay, no, okay, maybe I read it wrong.
No, but it's like ghost isn't even like,
okay, I misunderstood, okay.
I know, like I said, I'm sensitive right now,
and it's like, I just see like, I misread it, okay, I'm sorry.
I jumped to conclude, that's why I just timed out for a few minutes, because I was just like...
I followed it, and it misunderstood the comment, so...
But it's okay, I know, you can be mad at me, that's fine.
You understand, I had just been through like seven people saying kind of similar stuff, so I was like, oh no, not again, but...
Let me show you Matt, okay
You're not impressed but not mad, okay. Yeah, well if you just if you just understood I'm like I'm like a little bit touchy right now
So I didn't read it right
It ain't easy being in these sometimes
Well forgive me. The other people though are hidden.
I just feel like piled on sometimes.
I just love spewing nonsense. Yeah.
That's clear. That one's clear.
Really hope that is what I think it is
Yeah, hi, how you mean
know and when people say don't talk about something you know yeah and it's like
loving someone from afar thing that's what I do with my people that don't
like me I love them from afar you know it's like how do I like the thing is I
want to have relationship with people and
Don't want to love them from afar, but some people you have to right only if you have to I don't think that I have to in that situation
but
Go ahead
How I feeling um
I don't I don't want to bring anybody down, so I won't tell you how I'm feeling but
Oh, there's...
Feel like my cats will be
That's enough
Well, anyway, I put up the link and like, you know, I guess no one wants to come up and
You know, it's not having a good night anymore. So
Thanks for coming